let questions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which exercise boosts metabolism 24 hours a day, seven days a week?",
    choiceA: "strength training",
    choiceB: "Pilates",
    choiceC: "yoga",
    choiceD: "kickboxing",
    correct: "A",
  },

  {
    question:
      "Having a strong core — the muscles in your torso and pelvis — can help you to avoid:",
    choiceA: "falls",
    choiceB: "the flu",
    choiceC: "stress fractures",
    choiceD: "tennis elbow",
    correct: "A",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Yoga poses designed to stretch and strengthen your body are called:",
    choiceA: "stretches",
    choiceB: "asanas",
    choiceC: "chakras",
    choiceD: "pranas",
    correct: "B",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the best way to rehydrate after exercise?",
    choiceA: "eat fruit",
    choiceB: "drinks sports drinks",
    choiceC: "drink water",
    choiceD: "drink fruit juice",
    correct: "C",
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much high-intensity exercise should adults strive for each week?",
    choiceA: "30 minutes a week",
    choiceB: "120 minutes a week",
    choiceC: "140 minutes a week",
    choiceD: "75 minutes a week",
    correct: "D",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Aerobic exercise strengthen your.........?",
    choiceA: "heart",
    choiceB: "mind",
    choiceC: "body",
    choiceD: "soul",
    correct: "A",
  },  
  {
    question:
      "Chemicals that create a sense of well being and reduce feelings of stress.",
    choiceA: "food",
    choiceB: "drugs",
    choiceC: "endorphins",
    choiceD: "75 minutes a week",
    correct: "C",
  },  
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a type of aerobic exercise",
    choiceA: "running",
    choiceB: "lifting weights",
    choiceC: "biking",
    choiceD: "swimming",
    correct: "B",
  },  {
    question:
      "Calories are?",
    choiceA: "units of food energy",
    choiceB: "units of measurement",
    choiceC: "units of mass",
    choiceD: "units of diet",
    correct: "A",
  },  {
    question:
      "Exercise is a must for good _________________.",
    choiceA: "body tone",
    choiceB: "health",
    choiceC: "social skills",
    choiceD: "physical skills",
    correct: "B",
  },
];

module.exports = { questions };